Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Competitive Advertisements, Pre-55 Group, 1894-1957
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Container List
  - Food Products
    - Flour
      - Kitchen Craft, 1942-1944, (2 folders)
      - Minute Biscuit, 1932
      - Occident, 1914-1952, (4 folders)
      - Purity, 1929
      - Sno Sheen cake flour, 1949-1951, (2 folders)
      - Pillsbury, 1946-1954, (23 folders)
      - Pillsbury, 1949-1953, (2 folders) (Box 121)
      - Hecker's, 1930
      - Globe A1, 1931
      - Gold Medal, 1924
    - Fruit--Fresh
      - California Fruit Growers (Sunkist), 1923-1953, (15 folders)
      - Chiquita bananas, 1949-1952
      - Miscellaneous, 1919-1929
      - California Fruit Growers (Sunkist), 1927-1934, (5 folders) (Box 122)
      - Florida Citrus Commission, 1925-1950, (14 folders)
      - Atwood, 1931-1932
      - Bananas, 1926-1928
      - Unifruit bananas, 1927-1928
      - Banana Growers' Association, 1930
      - Bartlett pears, 1925
      - Blue Anchor, 1932
      - Blue Goose, 1928-1940, (2 folders)
      - Calavo, 1929-1931
      - California miscellaneous, 1939-1941
      - California Fruit Growers Exchange, 1927-1935, (2 folders)
      - Canadian apples, 1930
      - California Fruit Growers Exchange, 1931 (Box 123)
      - Fruit Dispatch Co., 1933-1940, (2 folders)
      - Fruit Industries, 1935
      - Georgia peaches, 1939
      - Imperial Valley canteloupes, 1926
      - Grapefruit, 1934
      - Indian River, 1931
      - Jim Hill apples, 1928-1930
      - Jonathan apples, 1928
      - Mel-O-Ripe, 1933-1939
      - Red & Gold vintages, 1932
      - Seald Sweet, 1927-1931, (2 folders)
      - Skookum apples, 1928-1934
      - State of Florida, 1936
      - Strawberries, 1930
      - Sunkist, 1924-1926
      - Tru Blu, 1933-1938
      - United Fruit Co., 1931-1940, (2 folders)
      - Vintner's grapes, 1931
      - Washington State apples, 1931-1938, (2 folders)
      - Pineapples, 1926-1928
      - Wenatchee apples, 1923
      - Miscellaneous, 1931-1954, (11 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1944-1946, (3 folders) (Box 124)
    - Ice
      - Knickerbocker, 1928-1935
      - Union, 1930-1933
      - Miscellaneous, 1928-1937
    - Pickles and olives
      - Miscellaneous, 1942-1954, (11 folders)
      - Heinz, 1923-1941
      - Pimentos, 1939
      - Sauerkraut, 1928-1932
    - Popcorn (includes Cracker Jack), 1930-1954, (7 folders)
    - Potato chips and potato salad, 1941-1950, (11 folders)
    - Meat and poultry
      - Poultry, 1932-1954, (12 folders)
      - Wilson, 1949-1950, (2 folders)
      - Mickelberry's, 1930-1933
      - Beechnut Bacon, 1920-1929
      - Boned chicken, 1921-1927
      - Hormel, 1950-1954, (5 folders)
      - Hormel, 1928-1949, (15 folders) (Box 125)
      - Howard's sausage, 1928
      - Hygrade, 1935-1949, (3 folders)
      - Underwood, 1927
      - Vogt's, 1916-1925
      - Jones, 1928-1939, (2 folders)
      - Land-O-Lakes, 1934
      - Long Island Duckling, 1927-1930
      - Mor, 1942
      - Morgan, 1932
      - Morris, 1928
      - Morrell, 1942
      - New England Pork, 1932
      - Oscar Mayer, 1950-1952, (3 folders)
      - Swift, 1941
      - Prudence, 1941
      - Skinless, 1953
      - Skinless, 1942-1952, (10 folders) (Box 126)
      - Smithfield, 1934-1936
      - Stahl-Meyer, 1933-1934
      - Underwood, 1928-1954, (9 folders)
      - Wilson, 1921-1953, (10 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1927-1934, (3 folders)
      - Meat extenders and tenderizers, 1953
      - Miscellaneous, 1939-1954, (13 folders) (Box 127)
      - Miscellaneous, 1950-1954, (2 folders) (Box 128)
    - Cooking fats and shortening
      - Armour, 1920-1936
      - Cottolene, 1918
      - Crisco, 1926-1942, (8 folders)
      - Crisco, 1922-1925 (Box 129)
      - Formay, 1932-1933
      - Prido, 1936
      - Snowdrift, 1924-1942, (4 folders)
      - Crisco, 1944-1951, (8 folders)
      - Crisco, 1952-1954, (3 folders) (Box 130)
      - Spry, 1939-1954, (14 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1954, (7 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1947, (5 folders) (Box 131)
      - Crisco, 1943
    - Soups
      - Campbell's, 1926-1934, (6 folders)
      - Campbell's, 1935-1945, (11 folders) (Box 132)
      - Heinz, 1930-1954, (19 folders) (Box 133)
      - Hormel, 1933-1940, (3 folders)
      - Lipton's, 1950-1954, (5 folders)
      - Lipton's, 1942-1949, (8 folders) (Box 134)
      - Miscellaneous, 1930-1954, (15 folders)
  - Gasoline, Oils and Lubricants
    - Alemite, 1948-1954, (7 folders)
    - Alemite, 1945-1947, (3 folders) (Box 135)
    - Atlantic, 1945-1953, (9 folders)
    - Cities Service, 1953-1954, (4 folders)
    - Conoco, 1946-1953, (6 folders)
    - Ethyl, 1943, 1951, (2 folders)
    - Gulf Oil, 1945-1951, (4 folders)
    - Mobilgas, 1951-1954, (2 folders)
    - Phillips 66, 1951-1954, (2 folders)
    - Union Oil Company of California, 1950
    - Miscellaneous, 1950-1953, (2 folders)
    - Gulf Oil, 1944-1949, (5 folders) (Box 136)
    - Macmillan Ring-Free motor oil, 1942-1953, (12 folders)
    - Mobilgas, 1944-1953, (5 folders)
    - Pennzoil, 1948-1954, (14 folders)
    - Pennzoil, 1943-1947, (5 folders) (Box 137)
    - Phillips 66, 1946-1953, (7 folders)
    - Quaker State, 1943-1954, (11 folders)
    - Conoco, 1950, 1954, (2 folders)
    - Sinclair, 1951-1954, (3 folders)
    - Texaco, 1951-1954, (2 folders)
    - Gulf Oil, 1953
    - Standard Oil, Inc., 1954
    - Cities Service, 1950-1951, (2 folders)
    - Standard Oil Company of California, 1951
    - Sunoco, 1951
    - Conoco, 1952 (Box 138)
    - Gulf Oil, 1952
    - Phillips 66, 1950
    - Sinclair, 1943-1952, (9 folders)
    - Socony-Vacuum (see also Mogilgas), 1945-1954, (12 folders)
    - Standard Oil, Inc., 1944-1953, (9 folders)
    - Socony-Vacuum (see also Mogilgas), 1943, 1952, (2 folders) (Box 139)
    - Standard Oil, Inc., 1943-1953, (20 folders)
    - Sunoco, 1939-1954, (11 folders)
    - Texaco, 1950-1953, (3 folders)
    - Texaco, 1944-1949, (6 folders) (Box 140)
    - Shell--competitive (various companies), 1943-1946
    - Tidewater Associated Oil Co. (Tydol--Veedol), 1945-1954, (7 folders)
    - Tidewater Associated Oil Co. (Tydol--Veedol), 1948-1950, (3 folders) (Box 141)
  - Household Goods
    - Cleaners and Cleaning Fluids
      - Boon, 1947
      - Ethyl, 1947
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1954, (7 folders)
      - Windex, 1946-1954, (8 folders)
    - Cleansers and Scouring Compounds
      - Bab-O, 1947-1949, (3 folders)
      - Bon Ami, 1947-1954, (8 folders)
      - Old Dutch Cleanser, 1951-1954, (4 folders)
      - Sunbrite, 1945-1947, (2 folders)
      - Spic & Span, 1947-1954, (7 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (2 folders)
      - Old Dutch Cleanser, 1947-1950, (4 folders) (Box 142)
      - Oakite, 1947-1954, (7 folders)
    - Clocks, 1948-1954, (7 folders)
    - Cloths (dish, polishing, etc.), 1950
    - Cooking Utensils
      - Club Aluminum, 1946-1954, (7 folders)
      - Mirro-Matic, 1946-1954, (9 folders)
      - Ek-Co pressure cooker, 1946-1954, (9 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947
      - Revere Ware, 1947-1954, (8 folders)
      - Wearever, 1948-1954, (7 folders)
      - Wearever, 1946-1947, (2 folders) (Box 143)
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1954, (6 folders)
    - Curtains
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1954, (7 folders)
      - Berkshire, 1949
    - Dinnerwear (China, Pottery, Plastic, etc.), 1954
    - Disinfectants
      - Clorox, 1947-1954, (8 folders)
      - Drano, 1947-1954, (8 folders)
      - Lysol, 1947-1954, (6 folders)
      - Sani-Flush, 1947-1954, (8 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1949-1953, (4 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1950, (4 folders) (Box 144)
    - Dyes
      - Tintex, 1947-1951, (4 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1953, (7 folders)
    - Anti-Noise Devices, 1953
    - Awnings, 1949-1954, (6 folders)
    - Air Cleaners, 1952
    - Bedding
      - Bedspreads and blankets
      - Miscellaneous, 1946-1954, (8 folders)
      - Sheets and pillowcases
        - Cannon, 1947-1954, (8 folders)
        - Pepperell, 1952-1954, (3 folders)
        - Pequot, 1952-1954, (3 folders)
        - Utica, 1952-1954, (3 folders)
        - Wamsutta, 1951-1952, (2 folders)
      - Mattresses--Simmons Beautyrest, 1948-1954, (7 folders)
      - Sheets and pillowcases
      - Simmons Beautyrest, 1947-1952, (2 folders) (Box 145)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1952, (6 folders)
      - Sheets and pillowcases
        - Pacific, 1947
        - Pepperell, 1947-1951, (5 folders)
        - Pequot, 1948-1951, (4 folders)
        - Utica, 1950
        - Fieldcrest, 1949
        - Pillows, 1951
        - Miscellaneous, 1949-1953, (5 folders)
        - Springmaid, 1950
      - Bedding miscellaneous, 1948
      - Bedspreads and blankets, 1949-1953, (5 folders)
      - Sheets and pillowcases
        - Miscellaneous, 1947-1954, (3 folders) (Box 146)
        - Utica, 1948-1949, (2 folders)
        - Wamsutta, 1947-1954, (5 folders)
      - Bedspreads and blankets, 1953
      - Mattresses
        - Simmons Beautyrest, 1953
        - Miscellaneous, 1953-1954, (2 folders)
    - Bleach (see also Household--Disinfectants)
      - Climalene, 1945-1950, (5 folders)
      - Clorox, 1946-1954, (9 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1953, (11 folders)
    - Bluing
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1954, (8 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1946, (4 folders) (Box 147)
      - Mrs. Stewart's, 1942
    - Bottles, Thermos, 1947-1954, (8 folders)
    - Brushes, Brooms and Mops, 1943-1953, (7 folders)
    - Candles, 1941-1954, (11 folders)
    - Bulbs, Sparklet, 1943
    - Chimes, 1946-1949, (3 folders)
    - China and pottery, 1942-1953, (13 folders)
    - Soap and Scouring Powder (See also Cleansers)
      - Bon Ami, 1926-1936, (5 folders)
      - Babbitt's Lye, 1922-1938, (2 folders)
      - Gillett's, 1935-1937
      - Lewis' Lye, 1920
      - Rex, 1934 (Box 148)
      - Lye miscellaneous, 1928-1942, (5 folders)
      - Ammo, 1928-1939, (4 folders)
      - Bab-O, 1925-1944, (17 folders)
      - Babbitt's Lye, 1929-1933, (2 folders)
      - Gillett's, 1932
      - Lewis' Lye, 1932-1934, (2 folders)
      - Be Bright, 1924-1926
      - Bon Ami, 1937-1946, (9 folders)
      - Bon Ami, 1922-1943, (9 folders) (Box 149)
      - Boraxo, 1936-1938
      - Bowlene, 1931-1932, (2 folders)
      - Brillo, 1928-1946, (9 folders)
      - Climax, 1930
      - Dawn, 1929
      - Drano, 1933-1942, (8 folders)
      - Drano, 1925-1932, (2 folders) (Box 150)
      - Flusho, 1941
      - Gold Dust, 1923-1933, (9 folders)
      - Gre Solvent, 1929-1930
      - Kitchen Klenzer, 1933-1936, (2 folders)
      - Kirkman, 1941
      - Gillett's, 1933-1934
      - Bab-O, 1930
      - Bon Ami, 1925
  - Electrical Goods
    - Household
      - Washing machines and driers, 1953
      - Emerson Electric, 1947
    - Industrial and institutional
      - General Electric, 1943-1944, (2 folders)
      - General Electric, 1942-1953, (10 folders) (Box 151)
      - Emerson Electric, 1949-1952, (3 folders)
      - McGraw Electric/Toastmaster, 1947-1951, (3 folders)
      - Mixers and blenders miscellaneous, 1954
      - Proctor, 1947-1953, (7 folders)
      - Sunbeam, 1948-1953, (4 folders)
      - Universal, 1952-1953, (2 folders)
      - Westinghouse, 1943
  - Beverages
    - Wines miscellaneous, 1946 (Box 152)
  - Industrial and institutional
    - General Electric, 1941, 1948, (2 folders)
    - Westinghouse, 1942-1949, (5 folders)
    - Bulbs and lamps--Sylvania, 1953
  - Household
    - General Electric, 1947-1953, (3 folders)
    - McGraw Electric/Toastmaster, 1952-1953, (2 folders)
    - Miscellaneous, 1948-1951, (4 folders)
    - Sunbeam, 1947, 1951, (2 folders)
    - Washing machines and driers, 1954
    - Westinghouse, 1949-1950, (3 folders)
    - Emerson Electric, 1953 (Box 153)
    - Washing machines and driers
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1952, (6 folders)
      - Easy, 1947-1953, (7 folders)
      - Frigidaire, 1948-1953, (6 folders)
      - General Electric, 1947-1953, (7 folders)
      - Launderall, 1947-1953, (7 folders)
      - Maytag, 1947-1953, (7 folders)
      - Thor, 1947-1953, (5 folders)
      - Westinghouse, 1950-1953, (7 folders)
  - Clocks, 1951
  - Industrial and institutional
    - Westinghouse, 1950-1953, (4 folders)
  - Household Goods
    - Floor covering
      - Linoleum and tile
        - Armstrong, 1954
        - Miscellaneous, 1954
      - Rugs and carpet
        - Alexander Smith, 1948-1951, (3 folders) (Box 154)
        - Bigelow, 1948-1954, (6 folders)
        - Gullistan, 1948-1954, (7 folders)
        - James Lees & Sons, 1941954, (7 folders)
        - Masland, 1951-1952, (2 folders)
        - Mohawk, 1949-1954, (4 folders)
        - Olson, 1952
        - Miscellaneous, 1951-1954, (4 folders)
        - Miscellaneous, 1947-1949, (3 folders) (Box 155)
    - Floor coverings miscellaneous, 1947-1952, (5 folders)
      - Linoleum and tile
        - Armstrong, 1950-1952, (3 folders)
        - Miscellaneous, 1947-1952, (4 folders)
    - Furniture
      - Daystrom, 1954
    - Fuel (See also Public Utilities)
      - Coal, Coke, etc., 1942-1946, (6 folders)
      - Kopper's Coke, 1939-1942, (2 folders)
      - Gas, 1942-1946, (4 folders)
      - Oil, 1945-1950, (5 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1937-1954, (7 folders)
    - Furniture
      - Miscellaneous, 1945-1954, (9 folders) (Box 156)
      - Daystrom, 1949-1953, (5 folders)
      - Drexel, 1950-1954, (5 folders)
      - Kroehler, 1953-1954, (2 folders)
      - Kroehler, 1949-1952, (4 folders) (Box 157)
      - Lane Cedar Chest, 1950-1954, (5 folders)
      - Mengel, 1950-1952, (3 folders)
      - Modernage, 1949-1950, (2 folders)
      - Pullman Couch, 1949-1951, (3 folders)
    - Floor Covering
      - Linoleum and tile, 1948
    - Laundry and Detergents
      - Fab, 1949-1953, (5 folders)
      - Fels Naptha, 1946-1954, (7 folders)
      - Fels Naptha, 1926-1951, (20 folders) (Box 158)
      - Fels Naptha, 1923-1924, (2 folders) (Box 159)
      - Glim, 1949-1951, (3 folders)
      - Ivory, 1939-1952, (19 folders)
      - Ivory, 1937-1939, (4 folders) (Box 160)
      - Rinso, 1927-1933, (6 folders)
      - Silk Eze, 1930
      - Silver Dust, 1947-1953, (6 folders)
      - Silver Dust, 1941-1942, (2 folders) (Box 161)
      - Soapine, 1925
      - Surf, 1950-1954, (5 folders)
      - Super Suds, 1943-1954, (9 folders)
      - Super Suds, 1932-1942, (8 folders) (Box 162)
      - Surf, 1949-1950, (3 folders)
      - Swan, 1942-1952, (12 folders)
      - Swerl, 1949-1952, (4 folders)
      - Tag, 1953
      - Tag, 1942-1952, (10 folders) (Box 163)
      - Tide, 1952-1953, (2 folders)
    - Ranges and stoves, 1944-1954, (11 folders)
    - Refrigerators, 1943-1951, (8 folders)
    - Refrigerators, 1949 (Box 164)
    - Rubber goods, 1943-1954, (10 folders)
    - Sewing Machines
      - Miscellaneous, 1940-1952, (11 folders)
      - Singer, 1940-1941, (2 folders)
      - White, 1941
    - Silver and Silverware
      - Miscellaneous, 1944-1954, (11 folders)
      - Community, 1948-1954, (6 folders)
      - Community, 1947 (Box 165)
      - Alvin, 1948-1953, (6 folders)
      - Gorham, 1947-1954, (8 folders)
      - Holmes & Edwards, 1947-1954, (8 folders)
      - International Sterling, 1948-1954, (7 folders)
      - Lunt, 1951-1954, (3 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1951
      - Lunt, 1948-1950, (3 folders) (Box 166)
      - Reed & Barton, 1953
      - 1847 Rogers Bros., 1947-1954, (8 folders)
      - Towle, 1948-1954, (7 folders)
      - Wallace Sterling, 1947-1954, (8 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1954
  - Tobacco Products
    - Pipe and Loose Tobacco
      - Philip Morris (Revelation, Bond Street), 1946 (Box 167)
      - Kentucky Club, 1949-1953
      - Christian Pepper, Dr. Grabow, C.B. Weber, John Middleton, 1947-1948
      - George Washington, Philip Morris Revelation, Dill's Best, John Middleton, 1947
      - Philip Morris (Revelation, Bond Street), 1945-1948
      - Sir Walter Raleigh/Old Gold, 1944-1954, (2 folders)
      - Country Doctor, 1944-1947
      - Briggs, 1945
      - Prince Albert, 1947-1950, (2 folders)
      - Edgeworth, 1949
      - Kentucky Club, 1954, (2 folders)
      - Prince Albert, 1948-1954, (3 folders)
      - Half & Half, 1926
      - Buckingham, Half & Half, 1926-1927
      - Model, Old Briar, 1953-1954
      - Edgeworth, 1948-1954
      - Rum and Maple, Tobin (Cookie Jar, Irish American), Christian Peper (Crosby Square, London Dock, Peper's), 1943 (Box 168)
      - Yello-Bole, Alfred Dunhill, Rogers Imports, Dobie's Four Square, Kirsten, Kent, 1944-1953
      - Briggs, Indian House, 1946-1954
      - Bond Street, Country Doctor, John Middleton, Old Virginia, 1943
      - Model, Bugler, Smoker's Haven/Lord Clive, Swan Ries, 1943
      - Liggett & Myers/Granger, Spud Imperial, 1943
      - Edgeworth, Revelation, 1943
      - Briggs, Prince Albert, 1940-1943
      - Crosby Square, London Dock, Whitehall, Sportsman, Brindley, Sugar Barrel, India House, Daniel Webster, 1944-1946
      - George Washington, Granger, Camel, Prince Albert, Holiday, 1944-1949
      - John Middleton, 1944-1946
      - Rum and Maple, John Surrey, Snow Apple, Brush Creek, John Middleton, Sutliff Tobacco/Heine's, 1944-1945
      - Revelation, Bond Street, 1944-1948, (2 folders)
      - Bond Street, Havana, Tampa, Rum and Maple, Zippo, Holiday, 1949-1957
      - Rum and Maple, Sir Walter Raleigh, Wedgewood, El Roi-Tan, Holiday, 1944-1949
      - Irish Castle, Donniford, Bergamot, Canadian Plug, Dill's Best, 1945-1948
      - Philip Morris (Revelation, Bond Street), 1945
    - Cigars
      - Blackstone, 1940-1945, (5 folders) (Box 169)
      - Admiration, 1940-1953, (12 folders)
      - Dutch Masters, 1941-1945, (5 folders) (Box 170)
    - Cigarettes--Cavalier, 1952
    - Cigars
      - Cinco, 1946-1947
      - Blackstone, 1944-1947
      - El Producto, 1946-1947, (4 folders) (Box 171)
      - Dunhill, 1940
      - Dutch Masters, 1943-1954, (7 folders)
      - El Producto, 1941-1948, (12 folders) (Box 172)
      - I. Lewis, 1943
      - R.G. Dunn, 1944
      - El Producto, 1949-1953, (4 folders) (Box 173)
      - Rey del Rey, 1944-1948 (Box 174)
      - Phillies, 1940-1952, (11 folders)
      - Harvester, 1954
      - Robt. Burns, 1940-1954, (12 folders) (Box 175)
      - Zippo, 1950
      - Virginia Rounds, 1950
      - Admiration, 1943
      - Dutch Masters, 1946 (Box 176)
      - Royalist, 1943-1947, (6 folders)
      - Tudor Arms, 1939-1942
      - Van Dyck, 1941
      - Webster, 1940-1952, (8 folders)
      - Cinco, 1945
      - Macy's Havana Humidor, 1940
      - Zippo, 1944
      - White Owl, 1940
      - Admiration, Van Dyck, Seidenberg, Harvester, Haddon Hall, 1948-1949 (Box 177)
      - Rialto, Gold Label, R.G. Dunn, Muriel, 1948
      - La Magnita, Dexter, Havana Dunhill, Prince Hamlet, La Palina, Garcia Grande, El Producto, 1948-1950
      - La Magnita, Harvester, Gold Label, 1949-1950
      - Van Dyck, Prince Hamlet, Haddon Hall, 1949-1950
      - Gold Label, El Producto, La Palina, Perfecto, Garcia y Vega, Nat Sherman, 1954
      - Robt. Burns, White Owl, Cigar Institute of America, Dunhill, 1950-1953
      - Gold Label, Mart, Van Dyck, The American, Havana Dunhill,, 1951
      - La Magnita, El Producto, Haddon Hall, Seidenberg, 1951
      - Harvester, White Owl, 1951
      - Reyes Havana Blunts, Nat Sherman Gold Label, Haddon Hall, Havana Dunhill, La Primadore, Joseph Jones, Garcia y Vega, 1952-1953
      - Cigar Institute of America, Gold Label, Harvester, 1952-1953
      - Royalton, King Edward, Wedgewood, Garcia y Vega, 1943
      - Webster, Havana Dunhill, 1943
      - Dutch Masters, Natural Bloom, J.A., Flamingo, Haddon Hall, La Coronada, Y-B, 1943
      - Robt. Burns, Rey del Rey, 1943
      - Dexter, Yankee, R.G. Sullivan's, La Palina, 1943
      - Dunhill, Dutch Masters, Prince Albert, Kind Edward, Nat Sherman, Garcia y Vega, 1945-1946 (Box 178)
      - Cinco, Robt. Burns, 1943-1947
      - La Primador, Royalist, Santa Fe, Garcia Grande, John Ruskin, Dry Climate, J.A., 1945-1947
      - Stetson, Kentucky Club, Dunhill, Roi-Tan, 1947-1950
      - Garcia y Vega, Seidenberg, La Magnita, 1945-1947
      - Habanello, Natural Bloom, Muriel, La Palina, 1945-1947
      - Air-Flo, Van Dyck, White Owl, Dutch Masters, Y-B, M&O, Nat Sherman, Seeman's, 1945-1947
      - Ignacio Haya, Tom Palmer, Bankable, Ameera, BCM, Coronada, Kilby, 1945-1947
      - Dexter, 7-204, Peter Schuyler, R.G. Dunn, 1945-1947
      - Robt. Burns, 1945-1947
      - Amerada, Haddon Hall, 1945-1947
    - Cigarettes
      - Camel, 1933-1934, (6 folders) (Box 179)
      - Camel, 1926-1933, (5 folders) (Box 180)
      - Camel, 1935, (2 folders) (Box 181)
      - Cavalier, 1949-1954, (5 folders)
      - Chelsea, 1943-1953, (10 folders)
      - Chesterfield, 1952-1954, (3 folders)
      - Deities, 1939
      - Domino, 1936-1942, (2 folders)
      - Dunhill, 1939
      - Du Maurier, 1951-1952, (2 folders)
      - Chesterfield, 1924-1930, (9 folders) (Box 182)
      - Chesterfield, 1944-1951, (8 folders) (Box 183)
      - Du Maurier, 1953-1954, (2 folders) (Box 184)
      - Embassy, 1949
      - Fatima, 1922-1953, (9 folders)
      - Fleetwood, 1942-1945, (4 folders)
      - Julep, 1942
      - Kent, 1952-1954, (3 folders)
      - Kentucky Winner, 1934-1935
      - Kool, 1933-1934, (4 folders)
      - Kool, 1945-1951, (7 folders) (Box 185)
      - Lucky Strike, 1948-1952, (2 folders)
    - Smokers Articles
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1954, (7 folders)
  - Toilet Goods
    - Baby Accessories, 1930-1931
    - Appliances: Mennen, 1932
    - Medicine: Mennen, 1930
    - Dennison, 1932
    - Miscellaneous, 1955
    - Toilet Articles, 1928-1929
    - Soap, 1922-1927
    - Barber Shops--Terminal, 1936-1941, (5 folders)
  - Tobacco Products
    - Cigarettes
      - L&M, 1954 (Box 186)
      - Life, 1948
      - Lords, 1953
      - Lucky Strike, 1946-1950, (5 folders)
      - Kool, 1937-1944, (8 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1951-1954, (4 folders) (Box 187)
    - Smokers Articles
      - Dunhill, 1947
      - Kaywoodie Briar, 1944-1954, (11 folders)
      - Lektrolite, 1944-1947, (3 folders)
      - Ronson Lighter, 1945-1954, (10 folders)
      - Yello-Bole,, 1944-1953, (7 folders)
      - Zippo Windproof Lighter, 1944-1954, (11 folders)
  - Toilet Goods
    - Barber Shops
      - Terminal, 1920-1933, (2 folders) (Box 188)
    - Bath Preparations, 1940-1954, (13 folders)
    - Bath Salts
      - Bathasweet, 1919-1939, (2 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1912-1939, (4 folders)
    - Brushes and Combs (includes toothbrushes)
      - Miscellaneous, 1944-1953, (8 folders)
      - D.D., 1940
      - Hutax, 1928
      - Pepsodent, 1941
      - Allbright, 1924-1925
    - Tissues, Cleansing
      - Kleenex, 1946
  - Tobacco Products
    - Cigarettes
      - Lucky Strike, 1951-1954, (4 folders) (Box 189)
      - Marlboro, 1952
      - Marvels; Marlboro, 1945-1953
      - Viceroys, 1950-1957 (Box 190)
      - King Sano, 1954
      - Tareyton, 1920-1936, (3 folders)
      - Viceroys, 1936-1957, (4 folders)
      - Winston, 1954
      - Miscellaneous, 1920-1953, (3 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1915-1939, (17 folders) (Box 191)
      - Miscellaneous, 1915-1950, (15 folders) (Box 192)
  - Toilet Goods
    - Combs, 1941 (Box 193)
    - Cold Creams
      - Cheramy, 1926
      - Colgates, 1915-1922
      - Colonial Dames, 1936-1937
      - Coty, 1930
      - Black and White, 1927
      - Boncilla Lemon Magnesia, 1928-1931
      - Dr. Charles Flesh Food, 1931
      - Caron, 1939-1940
    - Compacts, 1940-1941
    - Beauty Specialists and Beauty Preparations
      - Amor Skin, 1928-1929, (2 folders)
      - Arden, 1929-1947
      - Armand, 1930-1931
      - Harriet Hubbard Ayer, 1930-1953, (14 folders)
      - Bourjois, 1931-1942, (7 folders)
      - Bertie, 1928-1930